airgundepot.com 2014-07-03

# Privacy Policy

This privacy statement discloses the privacy practices for http://www.airgundepot.com

If you feel that this company is not abiding by its posted privacy policy, you should first contact Security Administrator by e-mail: inquiries@airgundepot.com.

#### Information Collection and Use

Airgun Depot is the sole owner of the information collected on this site. We will not sell, share, or rent this information to others in ways different from what is disclosed in this statement. Airgun Depot collects information from our users at several different points on our website.

#### Email

When you submit your email to us by placing an order, we store the information to send you order information, updates, verification requests, and other business related email. You may also receive our newsletter, which is sent out only occasionally containing airgun information, tips, specials, and announcements. If you do not want to subscribe to the newsletter, you may unsubscribe at any time by using the link provided on the bottom of each email. We have a strict NO SPAMMING policy, and we do not sell, share, or rent your email address with any third party or vendor. You do not have to place an order to subcribe to our email newsletter, simply click 'sign up' on our left navigation and provide the necessary information.

#### Order

We request information from the user on our order form. Here a user must provide contact information (like name and shipping address) and financial information (like credit card number, expiration date). This information is used for billing purposes and to fill customer’s orders. If we have trouble processing an order, this contact information is used to get in touch with the user.

#### Cookies

A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user’s computer containing information about the user. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information while on our site. One way we use cookies is to store your user name, but not billing information, thereby saving time while on our site.

Cookies are also used by analytic tools, such as Google Analytics Demographics and Interest Reporting, and shopping cart tools, such as the Yahoo! Shopping Cart. Third-party vendors, including Google, use first-party cookies (such as the Google Analytics cookie) and third-party cookies (such as the DoubleClick cookie) together to inform, optimize, and serve ads on sites across the Internet based on someone's past visits to our website. If you wish to not participate in Google's analytics and advertising features, you can [opt-out](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/) at any time.

Remember, cookies do not store any personally identifiable information. It is information that is used to make your browsing and shopping experience more enjoyable.

#### Log Files

We use IP addresses to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information.

#### Sharing

We do not share any of our customer information with any 3rd parties.

#### Links

This web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that Airgun Depot is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Web site.

#### Tell-A-Friend

If a user elects to use our referral service for informing a friend about our site, we ask them for the friend’s name and email address. Airgun Depot will automatically send the friend a one-time email inviting them to visit the site. Airgun Depot stores this information for the sole purpose of sending this one-time email. The friend will contact Airgun Depot at the URL shown in the e-mail to request the removal of this information from their database.

#### Security

This website takes every precaution to protect our users’ information. When users submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and off-line.

When our registration/order form asks users to enter sensitive information (such as credit card number and/or social security number), that information is encrypted and is protected with the best encryption software in the industry - SSL. While on a secure page, such as our order form, the lock icon on the bottom of Web browsers such as Netscape Navigator and Microsoft Internet Explorer becomes locked, as opposed to unlocked, or open, when you are just 'surfing'.

While we use SSL encryption to protect sensitive information online, we also do everything in our power to protect user-information off-line. All of our users’ information, not just the sensitive information mentioned above, is restricted in our offices. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, our billing clerk or a customer service representative) are granted access to personally identifiable information. Every quarter, as well as any time new policies are added, our employees are notified and/or reminded about the importance we place on privacy, and what they can do to ensure our customers’ information is protected. Finally, the servers that we store personally identifiable information on are kept in a secure environment, behind a locked cage.

If you have any questions about the security at our website, you can send an email to inquiries@airgundepot.com.

#### Notification of Changes

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on our Homepage so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under circumstances, if any, we disclose it. If at any point we decide to use personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time it was collected, we will notify users by way of an email. Users will have a choice as to whether or not we use their information in this different manner. We will use information in accordance with the privacy policy under which the information was collected.

 _This site is hosted by Yahoo! Store. Yahoo! hosts the store pages, ordering system, and order data. Yahoo! automatically collects order information but may only use this information in the aggregate. If you accessed this store through Yahoo! Shopping, Yahoo! also automatically collects information about your shopping experience. Please see the[Yahoo! Privacy Policy](http://info.yahoo.com/privacy/us/yahoo/details.html) for more information about how Yahoo! uses this information._
